Together nothing is impossible. Together nothing is forbidden.
The Dreamers is a drama, romance film directed by Bernardo Bertolucci.
When Isabelle and Theo invite Matthew to stay with them, what begins as a casual friendship ripens into a
sensual voyage of discovery and desire in which nothing is off limits and everything is possible.
Matthew, played by Michael Pitt.
Isabelle, played by Eva Green.
Theo, played by Louis Garrel.
Mother, played by Anna Chancellor.
Father, played by Robin Renucci.
Jean-Pierre Kalfon, played by Jean-Pierre Kalfon.
The Dreamers (French: Innocents: The Dreamers) is a 2003 erotic romantic drama film directed by Bernardo
Bertolucci from a screenplay by Gilbert Adair, based on Adair's 1988 novel The Holy Innocents.
An international co-production by companies from France, Italy and the United Kingdom, the film tells the story of an American university student
in Paris who, after meeting a peculiar brother and sister who are fellow film enthusiasts, becomes entangled in an erotic triangle.
It is set against the backdrop of the 1968 Paris student riots.
The film makes several references to various movies of classical and French New Wave cinema,
incorporating clips from films that are often imitated by the actors in particular scenes.
There are two versions: an uncut NC-17-rated version, and an
R-rated version that is about three minutes shorter.
It was the first credited film appearance of Eva Green,
and is considered her breakthrough role.
The film explores themes of hotel, first time, paris,
france, love triangle, students' movement.
The tone is emotional.